Welcome to Renew. Renew is designed to be a tool middle school students can use to share
their feelings and discuss things that happened in the past, which can sometimes be difficult
or awkward. Today we want to hear what you think of Renew. We want to hear things you
like or don't like about it. There are no right or wrong answers. We want you to take
it like this was something the school gave you to do. If there's anything you don't
want to answer, you can just skip it. Also, remember, if something comes up that you'd
like to talk to someone about, you can always tell the person who you're working with today.
After finishing Renew, you will complete a brief survey and then the person in the room
with you will ask you some wrap up questions. At any time you need a break or have a question,
you should feel free to ask the person watching it with you. Once you are done with the interview,
we will be able to pay you with the gift card at the email you have given us.